[
  {
    "Number": 1,
    "Question": "images/Calc2Q1.svg",
    "answer1": "images/two.svg",
    "answer2": "images/2x.svg",
    "answer3": "images/four.svg",
    "answer4": "images/xPow2.svg",
    "correct": "B",
    "hint": "",
    "input": false
  },
  {
    "Number": 2,
    "Question": "images/Calc2Q2.svg",
    "answer1": "images/1divCuberootXsquared.svg",
    "answer2": "images/x.svg",
    "answer3": "images/xPow2.svg",
    "answer4": "images/3DivXPow3.svg",
    "correct": "A",
    "hint": "",
    "input": false
  },
  {
    "Number": 3,
    "Question": "images/Calc2Q3.svg",
    "answer1": "images/xePowX-1.svg",
    "answer2": "images/xe.svg",
    "answer3": "images/",
    "answer4": "images/ePowX.svg",
    "correct": "D",
    "hint": "",
    "input": false
  },
  {
    "Number": 4,
    "Question": "images/Calc2Q4.svg",
    "answer1": "images/Calc2Q4A.svg",
    "answer2": "images/Calc2Q4B.svg",
    "answer3": "images/Calc2Q4C.svg",
    "answer4": "images/Calc2Q4D.svg",
    "correct": "C",
    "hint": "",
    "input": false
  },
  {
    "Number": 5,
    "Question": "images/Calc2Q5.svg",
    "answer1": "images/20.svg",
    "answer2": "images/5Div4.svg",
    "answer3": "images/5Div2.svg",
    "answer4": "images/four.svg",
    "correct": "C",
    "hint": "",
    "input": false,
    "numericalAnswer": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 6,
    "Question": "images/Calc2Q6.svg",
    "answer1": "images/Calc2Q6A.svg",
    "answer2": "images/Calc2Q6B.svg",
    "answer3": "images/5Div2.svg",
    "answer4": "images/four.svg",
    "correct": "A",
    "hint": "",
    "input": false
  },
  {
    "Number": 7,
    "Question": "images/Calc2Q7.svg",
    "answer1": "images/12.svg",
    "answer2": "images/Neg8.svg",
    "answer3": "images/Neg12.svg",
    "answer4": "images/6.svg",
    "correct": "C",
    "hint": "",
    "input": false
  },
  {
    "Number": 8,
    "Question": "images/Calc2Q8.svg",
    "answer1": "images/Calc2Q8A.svg",
    "answer2": "images/Calc2Q8B.svg",
    "answer3": "images/Calc2Q8C.svg",
    "answer4": "images/Calc2Q8D.svg",
    "correct": "B",
    "hint": "",
    "input": false
  },
  {
    "Number": 9,
    "Question": "images/Calc2Q9.svg",
    "answer1": "images/Calc2Q9A.svg",
    "answer2": "images/Calc2Q9B.svg",
    "answer3": "images/Calc2Q9C.svg",
    "answer4": "images/Calc2Q9D.svg",
    "correct": "A",
    "hint": "",
    "input": false
  },
  {
    "Number": 10,
    "Question": "images/Calc2Q10.svg",
    "answer1": "images/Calc2Q10A.svg",
    "answer2": "images/Calc2Q10B.svg",
    "answer3": "images/Calc2Q10C.svg",
    "answer4": "images/Calc2Q10D.svg",
    "correct": "D",
    "hint": "",
    "input": false
  },
  {
    "Number": 11,
    "Question": "images/Calc2Q11.svg",
    "answer1": "images/Calc2Q11A.svg",
    "answer2": "images/Calc2Q11B.svg",
    "answer3": "images/Calc2Q11C.svg",
    "answer4": "images/Calc2Q11D.svg",
    "correct": ["A", "B"],
    "hint": "",
    "chooseAll": true
  },
  {
    "Number": 12,
    "Question": "images/Calc2Q12.svg",
    "answer1": "images/Calc2Q12A.svg",
    "answer2": "images/Calc2Q12B.svg",
    "answer3": "images/Calc2Q12C.svg",
    "answer4": "images/Calc2Q12D.svg",
    "correct": ["A"],
    "hint": "",
    "chooseAll": true
  },
  {
    "Number": 13,
    "Question": "images/Calc2Q13.svg",
    "answer1": "images/Calc2Q13A.svg",
    "answer2": "images/Calc2Q13B.svg",
    "answer3": "images/Calc2Q13C.svg",
    "answer4": "images/Calc2Q13D.svg",
    "correct": "D",
    "hint": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 14,
    "Question": "images/Calc2Q14.svg",
    "answer1": "images/Calc2Q14A.svg",
    "answer2": "images/Calc2Q14B.svg",
    "answer3": "images/Calc2Q14C.svg",
    "answer4": "images/Calc2Q14D.svg",
    "correct": "B",
    "hint": ""
  },  {
    "Number": 15,
    "Question": "images/Calc2Q15.svg",
    "answer1": "images/Calc2Q15A.svg",
    "answer2": "images/Calc2Q15B.svg",
    "answer3": "images/Calc2Q15C.svg",
    "answer4": "images/Calc2Q15D.svg",
    "correct": "D",
    "hint": ""
  },{
    "Number": 16,
    "Question": "images/Calc2Q16.svg",
    "answer1": "images/Calc2Q16A.svg",
    "answer2": "images/Calc2Q16B.svg",
    "answer3": "images/Calc2Q16C.svg",
    "answer4": "images/Calc2Q15D.svg",
    "correct": "A",
    "hint": ""
  },{
    "Number": 17,
    "Question": "images/Calc2Q17.svg",
    "answer1": "images/Calc2Q17A.svg",
    "answer2": "images/Calc2Q17B.svg",
    "answer3": "images/Calc2Q17C.svg",
    "answer4": "images/Calc2Q17D.svg",
    "correct": "B",
    "hint": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 18,
    "Question": "images/Calc2Q18.svg",
    "answer1": "images/Calc2Q18A.svg",
    "answer2": "images/Calc2Q18B.svg",
    "answer3": "images/Calc2Q17C.svg",
    "answer4": "images/Calc2Q18D.svg",
    "correct": "C",
    "hint": ""
  },{
    "Number": 19,
    "Question": "images/Calc2Q19.svg",
    "answer1": "images/Calc2Q19A.svg",
    "answer2": "images/Calc2Q19B.svg",
    "answer3": "images/Calc2Q17C.svg",
    "answer4": "images/Calc2Q19D.svg",
    "correct": "B",
    "hint": ""
  },
  {
    "Number": 20,
    "Question": "images/Calc2Q20.svg",
    "answer1": "images/Calc2Q20A.svg",
    "answer2": "images/Calc2Q20B.svg",
    "answer3": "images/Calc2Q20C.svg",
    "answer4": "images/Calc2Q20D.svg",
    "correct": "C",
    "hint": ""
  },{
    "Number": 21,
    "Question": "images/Calc2Q21.svg",
    "input": true,
    "inputAnswer": "1.31"
  },{
    "Number": 22,
    "Question": "images/Calc2Q22.svg",
    "input": true,
    "inputAnswer": "1/6"
  },{
    "Number": 23,
    "Question": "images/Calc2Q23.svg",
    "input": true,
    "inputAnswer": "-8.33"
  },{
    "Number": 24,
    "Question": "images/Calc2Q24.svg",
    "input": true,
    "inputAnswer": "8"
  },{
    "Number": 25,
    "Question": "images/Calc2Q25.svg",
    "input": true,
    "inputAnswer": "36"
  }
]
